{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","address":"5200 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Detroit Institute of Arts","licenseNumber":"043345","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/10/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000C4C09FB925C454C0E02DAA61D92D4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45178","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","inspectionDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"131","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"45178","inspectionDate":"7/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"By the Sink (food prep)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"inspectionid":"45178","inspectionDate":"7/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"and the Serving area","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-07-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"},{"inspectionid":"45178","inspectionDate":"7/26/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Above 194 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (1st FLOOR)","subLocation":"Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-02-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."}]},{"inspectionid":"41127","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","inspectionDate":"2017-12-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41127","inspectionDate":"12/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN/BASEMENT","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"41127","inspectionDate":"12/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Above 194 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN (1st FLOOR)","subLocation":"Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"inspectionid":"41127","inspectionDate":"12/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"4-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) The temperature of the wash solution in spray type warewashers that use hot water to SANITIZERS may not be less than:     \r\n(1) For a stationary rack, single temperature machine, 74°C (165°F);(Pf)   \r\n(2) For a stationary rack, dual temperature machine, 66°C (150°F); (Pf)   \r\n(3) For a single tank, conveyor, dual temperature machine, 71°C (160°F);(Pf) or\r\n(4) For a multitank, conveyor, multitemperature machine, 66°C (150°F).(Pf)  \r\n(B) The temperature of the wash solution in spray-type warewashers that use chemicals to SANITIZE may not be less than 49°C (120°F). (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Dish machine wash solution temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 160 degrees F","subProblem":"For hot water sanitizing machine Single tank, conveyor, dual temperature","location":"KITCHEN (1st FLOOR)","subLocation":"Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"inspectionid":"41127","inspectionDate":"12/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN/BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"41127","inspectionDate":"12/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"41127","inspectionDate":"12/28/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"Taco Station","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"38916","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","inspectionDate":"2017-06-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38916","inspectionDate":"6/2/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37162","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","inspectionDate":"2016-11-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37162","inspectionDate":"11/9/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN/BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"inspectionid":"37162","inspectionDate":"11/9/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2330","name":"Detroit Institute of Arts -Cafe DIA","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Throughout Wall(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2330"}}